Mark Carney, the PM of Canada, says we're done being married to the United States.
Switzerland says we're against whatever the United States is on.
The United States is like starting all these wars.
And what I know it looks like is like, wow, the United States is so bad that everyone hates us.
That's not, I don't believe that's what's happening.
I believe what's happening is that the folks that use the United States are making the United States look like chaos, look like drama, so that they can step in and say, well, we are now going to run shit.
We're going to control the United States now, even though they always have been.
But it was surreptitious and behind the scenes and from the seat of Europe.
And that is going to change soon.
And those folks are based in Switzerland.
And those folks already run Canada because the Queen is on Canadian money because Canada is a part of the British Commonwealth.
You see Canada making deals with China and you see Russia saying, OK, guys, like I'm ready to be cool with you all again.
And you think probably see.
Everybody is cool except for the U.S.
And that's by design.
It's by design.
To manufacture the consent of U.S.
Americans for what's to come.
We are on the precipice of a regime change here in the United States.
And it doesn't even matter if I'm right.
Because not enough folks are prescient enough to be able to come together enough to try to stop it.
So I'm basically just venting to my phone right now.